<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>your-site-name</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on your-site-name</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-KR</language>
    <managingEditor>your-email (jonthelaion)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>your-email (jonthelaion)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 23:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing Data Science (Book)</title>
      <link>/post/doing-data-science-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>your-email (jonthelaion)</author>
      <guid>/post/doing-data-science-book/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1 - Introduction: What Is Data Science?With many years of experience in both academia and industry, authors Cathy O’Neil &amp;amp; Rachel Schutt look beyond the hype to explore what the data science discipline looks like in practice.
They also explore an idea that is often overlooked when speaking about data science - that building models and working with data is not value-neutral. You choose the problems you will work on, you make assumptions in those models, you choose metrics, and you design the algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Resources</title>
      <link>/post/r-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>your-email (jonthelaion)</author>
      <guid>/post/r-resources/</guid>
      <description>BlogsCathy O’Neil BlogData Science CentralR MarkdownCreating Websites with R Markdown (Currently Reading)General Data ScienceDoing Data ScienceColumbia - Applied Data ScienceLearning RThe Art of R Programming - Norman Matloff (No Starch Press)R for Everyone: Advanced Analytics and GraphicsLearning PythonLearning Python - Mark Lutz and David Ascher (O’Reilley)Python for Data Analysis - Wes McKinney (O’Reilley)MathLinear Algebra and Its Applications - Gilbert Strang (Cengage Learning)VisualisationThe Elements of Grpahing Data - William Cleveland (Hobart Press)Visualize This: The FLowingData Guide to Design, Visualization, and Statistics - Nathan Yau (Wiley)The VIsual Display of Quantitative Information - Edward Tufte (Graphics Press)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>your-email (jonthelaion)</author>
      <guid>/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Creating this blog to journal my progress towards becoming an applied statistician.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>